<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UglyFeed RSS</title><link>https://github.com/fabriziosalmi/UglyFeed</link><description>A dynamically generated feed using UglyFeed.</description><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/fabriziosalmi/UglyFeed/main/examples/uglyfeed-source-1.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><author>UglyFeed</author><category>Technology</category><copyright>UglyFeed</copyright><item><title>方佳瑞赞同了回答: 机器学习中有哪些形式简单却很巧妙的idea？</title><description>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. Extract 3 Keywords of the Article&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;机器学习 (Machine Learning)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;巧妙的idea (Clever Ideas)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;实验技巧 (Experimental Techniques)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2. Concise and Informative Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This article discusses various clever but often unethical techniques used in machine learning research to enhance experimental results. It covers methods such as increasing batch size, training epochs, and model complexity to artificially inflate performance metrics. The article also highlights manipulations in hyperparameters, model architecture, and testing methodologies to achieve better reported results. These techniques include using different loss functions, adding attention layers, and selectively reporting favorable metrics. The author emphasizes the importance of transparency and ethical practices in machine learning research to ensure the validity and reliability of published results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;3. Outline of the Whole Article&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;算力碾压&lt;/strong&gt; (Compute Power Overwhelm): Techniques to increase computational power and model complexity to boost performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;超参数调整&lt;/strong&gt; (Hyperparameter Tuning): Manipulating learning rates, optimizer parameters, and random seeds to optimize results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;模型架构调整&lt;/strong&gt; (Model Architecture Adjustments): Changing activation functions, adding attention mechanisms, and modifying normalization layers to improve performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;训练集和测试集差异处理&lt;/strong&gt; (Handling Differences Between Training and Test Sets): Designing data augmentation and distribution adjustments to enhance model performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;测试方法&lt;/strong&gt; (Testing Methods): Selectively reporting favorable metrics, using different hardware, and manipulating test conditions to outperform baselines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;终极方法&lt;/strong&gt; (Ultimate Methods): Copying others' methods with name changes, claiming high performance without open-source code, and writing papers without experiments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;4. Overall Recommendation Degree&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;D&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pros:&lt;/strong&gt;
- Provides a comprehensive list of techniques used in machine learning research.
- Highlights the importance of ethical practices in research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cons:&lt;/strong&gt;
- Focuses heavily on unethical practices, which may not be constructive for the field.
- Lacks depth in discussing the implications and consequences of these practices.
- Does not offer solutions or guidelines for more ethical research practices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;5. Who May Be Interested in This Content&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Machine learning researchers and practitioners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Academics and students in the field of artificial intelligence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ethical AI advocates and policymakers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;6. Thought-Provoking Questions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the potential long-term consequences of using unethical techniques in machine learning research?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How can the research community promote and enforce ethical standards in machine learning publications?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Can you identify any specific examples from recent machine learning papers where these techniques might have been used, and how could they be detected?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 09:35:02 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.zhihu.com/question/347847220/answer/26536819499</guid></item><item><title>Ofcom warns tech firms after chatbots imitate Brianna Ghey and Molly Russell</title><description>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. Keywords&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chatbots&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Online Safety Act&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Impersonation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2. Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ofcom, the UK's communications regulator, has issued a warning to tech firms about the potential legal consequences of user-created chatbots that impersonate real or fictional individuals. This warning comes after distressing incidents where users on the Character.AI platform created avatars mimicking deceased British teenagers Brianna Ghey and Molly Russell. According to Ofcom, such content could violate the UK's Online Safety Act, which aims to protect users from harmful online content. The regulator emphasizes the importance of tech companies ensuring that their platforms do not facilitate the creation of harmful or misleading content, particularly when it involves sensitive topics like suicide or the deceased.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;3. Outline&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;: Ofcom warns tech firms about the legal risks of chatbots impersonating real or fictional people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background&lt;/strong&gt;: Distressing incidents on Character.AI where users created avatars of deceased British teenagers Brianna Ghey and Molly Russell.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Regulatory Action&lt;/strong&gt;: Ofcom issues guidance under the UK Online Safety Act to prevent harmful content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Implications&lt;/strong&gt;: Tech companies must ensure their platforms do not facilitate the creation of harmful or misleading content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support Resources&lt;/strong&gt;: Contact information for crisis support services in the UK, Ireland, US, and Australia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;4. Overall Recommendation Degree: B&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pros&lt;/strong&gt;:
- The article addresses a significant and timely issue regarding the ethical and legal implications of AI-generated content.
- It provides clear guidance from a regulatory body (Ofcom) and highlights the importance of responsible content creation.
- The inclusion of contact information for crisis support services shows a responsible approach to sensitive topics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cons&lt;/strong&gt;:
- The article could provide more detailed examples of how the Online Safety Act will be enforced in such cases.
- It lacks a broader discussion on the technological and societal implications of AI-generated content.
- The article does not explore the perspectives of tech companies or users, which could offer a more balanced view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;5. Who May Be Interested in This Content&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tech companies and developers working on AI and chatbot technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Policymakers and regulators involved in online safety and digital laws.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Families and advocates of individuals affected by online impersonation and harmful content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Researchers and ethicists studying the impact of AI on society.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;6. Thought-Provoking Questions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What specific measures can tech companies implement to prevent the creation of harmful or misleading chatbot content?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How should the balance between free speech and online safety be maintained in the context of AI-generated content?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the potential long-term societal impacts of widespread use of chatbots that can convincingly impersonate real or fictional individuals?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 09:34:46 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2024/nov/09/ofcom-warns-tech-firms-after-chatbots-imitate-brianna-ghey-and-molly-russell</guid></item></channel></rss>