<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UglyFeed RSS</title><link>https://github.com/fabriziosalmi/UglyFeed</link><description>A dynamically generated feed using UglyFeed.</description><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/fabriziosalmi/UglyFeed/main/examples/uglyfeed-source-1.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><author>UglyFeed</author><category>Technology</category><copyright>UglyFeed</copyright><item><title>科技爱好者周刊（第 328 期）：AI 模型不是一门好生意</title><description>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. 关键词&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AI 模型&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;成本&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;商业模式&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2. 精炼摘要&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;本文探讨了AI模型行业的商业困境，指出尽管AI模型具有巨大的潜力，但高昂的成本和快速贬值的特点使其难以成为一个可持续的商业模式。文章提到微软和OpenAI等公司纷纷涨价，反映出AI模型的巨大开支。此外，AI模型缺乏规模经济效应，且需要不断更新以保持竞争力，这使得公司难以盈利。同时，开源模型的兴起也加剧了市场竞争，使得商业模型的垄断优势难以维持。因此，对于考虑进入AI模型领域的公司，文章建议应谨慎评估风险。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;3. 文章大纲&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;封面图&lt;/strong&gt;：上海南站正在改造，车站的北半部在施工，南半部正常运营。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI 模型不是一门好生意&lt;/strong&gt;：微软和OpenAI涨价，反映了AI模型的高昂成本。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;高额投入&lt;/strong&gt;：AI模型需要大量资金，且投入巨大。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;缺乏规模经济&lt;/strong&gt;：AI模型越大，单位成本反而更高。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;快速贬值&lt;/strong&gt;：新模型不断推出，旧模型快速贬值。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;无法保持垄断优势&lt;/strong&gt;：云服务商的资源可以被任何人租用，难以形成持久的竞争优势。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;应对策略&lt;/strong&gt;：筹集更多资金，使模型差异化。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;豆包 MarsCode 系列活动&lt;/strong&gt;：介绍豆包 MarsCode 的编程助手及其即将举行的活动。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;科技动态&lt;/strong&gt;：介绍几项有趣的科技动态，包括树莓派掌上电脑、超声波洗澡机和升缩鞋。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;文章推荐&lt;/strong&gt;：推荐几篇科技文章，涉及Astro框架、Phoenix LiveView、机上WiFi定位等。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;工具推荐&lt;/strong&gt;：推荐一些实用的工具，如Bananas、jsontr.ee等。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI 相关&lt;/strong&gt;：介绍一些AI相关的资源，如Bylo.ai、Color Diffusion等。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;资源推荐&lt;/strong&gt;：推荐一些有用的资源，如Hi Speaking、In Pieces等。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;图片&lt;/strong&gt;：展示乐高面板和老照片中人们不微笑的原因。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;文摘&lt;/strong&gt;：讨论哺乳动物的心跳速率与体型的关系。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;言论&lt;/strong&gt;：引用几位名人的观点，涉及比特币、尼采、内部平台效应等。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;往年回顾&lt;/strong&gt;：回顾过去几年的科技话题。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;文档信息&lt;/strong&gt;：提供版权声明和发表日期。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;4. 推荐度&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;B&lt;/strong&gt;
- &lt;strong&gt;优点&lt;/strong&gt;：文章内容丰富，涵盖了AI模型行业的多个方面，逻辑清晰，分析透彻，提供了丰富的数据和实例支持。
- &lt;strong&gt;缺点&lt;/strong&gt;：部分内容较为简略，例如应对策略部分可以进一步展开；某些技术细节的解释不够深入，可能导致非专业人士理解困难。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;5. 感兴趣的读者&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI研究人员和开发者&lt;/strong&gt;：对AI模型的成本和商业模式感兴趣。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;科技投资者&lt;/strong&gt;：关注AI行业的投资前景和风险。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;科技爱好者&lt;/strong&gt;：对最新的科技动态和技术趋势感兴趣。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;6. 思考题&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;为什么AI模型的成本会随着模型规模的增大而增加？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;这涉及到计算资源的需求和模型优化的难度。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;开源模型的兴起对商业AI模型公司有何影响？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;开源模型的出现使得商业模型的竞争力下降，用户可能会转向免费的开源选项。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI模型公司如何在激烈的竞争中保持竞争优势？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;除了筹集资金，公司还需要不断创新，使模型差异化，并提高用户体验。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 03:51:29 GMT</pubDate><guid>http://www.ruanyifeng.com/blog/2024/12/weekly-issue-328.html</guid></item><item><title>Trump picks venture capitalist David Sacks as AI and crypto ‘czar’</title><description>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. Keywords&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;David Sacks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Artificial Intelligence (AI)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Crypto Czar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2. Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump has nominated David Sacks, a venture capitalist and former PayPal COO, as the White House AI and crypto czar. This appointment continues Trump's pattern of rewarding significant donors with influential positions. Sacks, known for his Silicon Valley connections, hosted a fundraising event at his San Francisco mansion in June, which raised $12 million for Trump's campaign. The nomination highlights the importance Trump places on AI and cryptocurrency as key areas for future American competitiveness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;3. Outline&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;: Donald Trump announces the nomination of David Sacks as the White House AI and crypto czar.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background on David Sacks&lt;/strong&gt;: Sacks is a venture capitalist and former PayPal COO who hosted a major fundraising event for Trump.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fundraising Event&lt;/strong&gt;: The event at Sacks' San Francisco mansion raised $12 million for Trump's campaign.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trump's Pattern&lt;/strong&gt;: This nomination is part of Trump's trend of rewarding big donors with political power.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Significance&lt;/strong&gt;: The appointment underscores the importance of AI and cryptocurrency in future American competitiveness.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;4. Overall Recommendation Degree: B&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pros:&lt;/strong&gt;
- The article provides a clear and concise overview of the nomination and its context.
- It highlights the significance of AI and cryptocurrency in future American competitiveness.
- The connection between political donations and appointments is well-explained.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cons:&lt;/strong&gt;
- The article could provide more detailed information about Sacks' qualifications and experience in AI and cryptocurrency.
- There is limited discussion on the potential implications of this appointment for policy and governance.
- The article does not explore potential criticisms or alternative viewpoints.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;5. Who May Be Interested in This Content&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Political Analysts&lt;/strong&gt;: Those interested in the intersection of politics and technology.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tech Enthusiasts&lt;/strong&gt;: Individuals following developments in AI and cryptocurrency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Campaign Finance Experts&lt;/strong&gt;: People studying the influence of big donors in political appointments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;6. Thought-Provoking Questions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What specific qualifications does David Sacks bring to the role of AI and crypto czar, and how do they align with the challenges in these fields?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How might the appointment of a big donor as a high-ranking official impact public trust in government decisions related to AI and cryptocurrency?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the potential long-term implications of prioritizing AI and cryptocurrency as key areas for American competitiveness, and how might other countries respond?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 03:50:53 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2024/dec/05/trump-david-sacks-ai-crypto</guid></item></channel></rss>