<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UglyFeed RSS</title><link>https://github.com/fabriziosalmi/UglyFeed</link><description>A dynamically generated feed using UglyFeed.</description><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/fabriziosalmi/UglyFeed/main/examples/uglyfeed-source-1.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><author>UglyFeed</author><category>Technology</category><copyright>UglyFeed</copyright><item><title>更完善的「简悦 · 更新日志」</title><description>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. Keywords&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Telegram Channel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSS Optimization&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Follow Subscription&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2. Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The article discusses the latest updates to the Jianyue (简悦) platform, which is primarily used for releasing changelogs and updates. Jianyue has introduced a new platform based on its Telegram Channel to enhance user experience across different network environments. This platform offers real-time updates, consistent content with the Telegram Channel, global CDN for faster access, support for images, permanent links, and search functionality. These improvements aim to make the update information more accessible and user-friendly for Jianyue's growing user base.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;3. Outline&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;: Jianyue's Telegram Channel is the primary channel for updates and changelogs, with over 6K users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Previous Updates&lt;/strong&gt;: Jianyue has previously optimized RSS and added Follow subscription features.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Platform&lt;/strong&gt;: Introduction of a new platform based on the Telegram Channel, providing consistent and real-time updates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Features&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Content consistency with the Telegram Channel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Real-time updates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Global CDN for fast access.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support for images from the Telegram Channel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Permanent links for specific posts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Search functionality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;: The new platform aims to enhance user experience and accessibility for Jianyue's users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;4. Recommendation Degree: B&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pros&lt;/strong&gt;:
- The article clearly outlines the new features and improvements, making it easy for users to understand the benefits.
- The introduction of a new platform based on the Telegram Channel addresses the needs of users in different network environments.
- The addition of features like global CDN and search functionality enhances user experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cons&lt;/strong&gt;:
- The article lacks detailed technical explanations or user testimonials that could provide deeper insights into the effectiveness of the new features.
- There is no mention of potential issues or limitations with the new platform.
- The article does not discuss future plans or potential improvements, which could be useful for users and developers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;5. Who May Be Interested&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jianyue Users&lt;/strong&gt;: Current and potential users of the Jianyue platform who want to stay updated on the latest features and improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developers&lt;/strong&gt;: Developers interested in creating similar platforms for their own projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tech Enthusiasts&lt;/strong&gt;: Individuals interested in the latest updates and innovations in tech platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;6. Thought-Provoking Questions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How does the new platform based on the Telegram Channel improve the user experience compared to previous methods?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the potential limitations of the new platform, and how might they be addressed in future updates?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In what ways could the search functionality and global CDN be further optimized to enhance the user experience?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 09:39:34 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://zhuanlan.zhihu.com/p/7035029609</guid></item><item><title>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2716400/The_Rise_of_the_Golden_Idol/ 已出已玩，比前作更上一层楼，冲！ 还可以买 DLC pass，包括 25 年 Q1 - Q3 会出的...</title><description>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. Keywords&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Rise of the Golden Idol&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DLC Pass&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Detective Saga&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2. Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The Rise of the Golden Idol" is a standalone sequel to the award-winning detective saga, set in the 1970s. The game offers players the opportunity to solve 20 strange cases involving crime, death, and depravity. It builds upon the success of its predecessor, offering enhanced gameplay and a more immersive experience. Additionally, players can purchase a DLC pass that includes four upcoming DLCs, each adding substantial content to the game. The DLC pass is priced the same as the base game, suggesting that the combined content of the DLCs is equivalent to another full game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;3. Outline&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;: "The Rise of the Golden Idol" is a standalone sequel to the award-winning detective saga.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Game Overview&lt;/strong&gt;: Players will uncover the truth behind 20 strange cases of crime, death, and depravity in the 1970s.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhancements&lt;/strong&gt;: The game builds upon the success of its predecessor with improved gameplay and immersion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DLC Pass&lt;/strong&gt;: A DLC pass is available, including four upcoming DLCs that add significant content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pricing&lt;/strong&gt;: The DLC pass is priced the same as the base game, indicating substantial additional content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;4. Overall Recommendation Degree: B&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pros&lt;/strong&gt;:
- The game offers a rich and immersive detective experience with 20 unique cases.
- The DLC pass provides substantial additional content, making it a good value for money.
- Builds upon the success of its predecessor, enhancing the gameplay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cons&lt;/strong&gt;:
- The summary does not provide detailed information about the specific improvements or new features in the game.
- There is no mention of player reviews or critical reception, which could help gauge the game's quality.
- The pricing comparison is somewhat vague and lacks concrete details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;5. Who May Be Interested in This Content&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fans of detective games and mystery-solving narratives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Players who enjoyed the previous installment of the series.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gamers looking for a rich and immersive single-player experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;6. Thought-Provoking Questions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What specific improvements does "The Rise of the Golden Idol" offer compared to its predecessor?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do the four upcoming DLCs enhance the overall gameplay experience, and what new elements do they introduce?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In what ways does the game's setting in the 1970s contribute to the narrative and gameplay mechanics?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 09:39:02 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://t.me/LinghaoCh/895</guid></item></channel></rss>