<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UglyFeed RSS</title><link>https://github.com/fabriziosalmi/UglyFeed</link><description>A dynamically generated feed using UglyFeed.</description><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/fabriziosalmi/UglyFeed/main/examples/uglyfeed-source-1.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><author>UglyFeed</author><category>Technology</category><copyright>UglyFeed</copyright><item><title>Is Python Really That Slow?</title><description>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. Keywords&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Python Performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Benchmarking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PyPy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2. Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The article explores the performance of Python by running benchmarks against various Python versions and other languages like Node.js and Rust. The author, who typically finds Python to be a fast-to-write and maintainable language despite its runtime performance penalties, conducts CPU-intensive tests using Fibonacci numbers and bubble sort algorithms. The results show significant performance improvements in Python 3.11 and beyond, with PyPy outperforming CPython versions by a large margin. Rust consistently performs the best, but the author notes that Python's performance is improving and that PyPy is particularly impressive. The article also discusses common misconceptions about Python performance, such as the impact of the Global Interpreter Lock (GIL) and the potential of the Just-In-Time (JIT) compiler in Python 3.13.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;3. Outline&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;: The author explains their perspective on Python's performance and the context for conducting benchmarks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fibonacci Numbers Benchmark&lt;/strong&gt;: The author describes the setup and results of the Fibonacci numbers benchmark, showing significant performance differences between Python versions and other languages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubble Sort Benchmark&lt;/strong&gt;: Another benchmark is conducted using the bubble sort algorithm, with results indicating varying performance across Python versions and a strong showing from PyPy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mac Benchmarks&lt;/strong&gt;: The author repeats the benchmarks on a Mac with an ARM-based CPU to check for platform-specific performance differences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Common Misconceptions&lt;/strong&gt;: The article addresses common myths about Python performance, including the role of asyncio, the JIT compiler, and the GIL.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benchmarking Code&lt;/strong&gt;: The author provides the code and scripts used for the benchmarks, allowing readers to replicate the results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;: The author summarizes the findings, highlighting the performance improvements in recent Python versions and the potential of PyPy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;4. Recommendation Degree: B&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pros:&lt;/strong&gt;
- The article provides detailed and well-structured benchmarks, which are valuable for understanding Python's performance.
- The author addresses common misconceptions about Python performance, which is useful for developers.
- The inclusion of code and scripts for replication adds credibility and transparency to the findings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cons:&lt;/strong&gt;
- The benchmarks are limited to two specific algorithms, which may not fully represent real-world performance.
- The article does not explore the impact of optimized libraries (e.g., NumPy) on Python performance, which could provide a more comprehensive view.
- Some technical details, such as the exact configurations of the testing environment, could be more clearly explained.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;5. Who May Be Interested in This Content&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Python Developers&lt;/strong&gt;: Those interested in optimizing their Python code or understanding the performance characteristics of different Python versions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Performance Enthusiasts&lt;/strong&gt;: Individuals who are generally interested in benchmarking and comparing the performance of different programming languages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Educators and Students&lt;/strong&gt;: Those teaching or learning about programming languages and performance optimization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;6. Thought-Provoking Questions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the key factors that contribute to the performance differences between CPython and PyPy, and how might these factors be leveraged in real-world applications?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do the performance characteristics of Python change when using optimized libraries like NumPy, and how does this compare to the raw performance benchmarks presented in the article?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Given the results of the benchmarks, what are the potential implications for choosing Python over other languages for CPU-intensive tasks, and how might these choices vary depending on the specific use case?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 21:37:25 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://blog.miguelgrinberg.com/post/is-python-really-that-slow</guid></item><item><title>AI poetry rated better than poems written by humans, study shows</title><description>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. Keywords&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AI Poetry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Human Poetry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Non-Expert Readers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2. Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A study conducted by researchers at the University of Pittsburgh found that non-expert poetry readers often preferred AI-generated poems over those written by humans. Participants were shown poems by 10 famous English-language poets and AI-generated poems in the same styles. The results indicated that about 75% of human-written poems were correctly identified, while AI-generated poems were often mistaken for human-authored ones. Contrary to previous research, participants also rated AI-generated poems as higher in overall quality. The study suggests that non-expert readers find AI-generated poems more straightforward and accessible, though the complexity and opacity of human poetry are part of its appeal. The authors propose that AI-generated poems, due to their clarity, might increase interest in poetry among non-expert readers. However, poet Joelle Taylor argues that true poetry involves elements like empathy and revelation, which AI cannot fully capture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;3. Outline&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;: A study by the University of Pittsburgh shows that non-expert readers often prefer AI-generated poems over human-written ones.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Methodology&lt;/strong&gt;: Participants were shown poems by 10 famous poets and AI-generated poems in similar styles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Results&lt;/strong&gt;: About 75% of human-written poems were correctly identified, and AI-generated poems were rated higher in quality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Discussion&lt;/strong&gt;: Non-expert readers find AI-generated poems more straightforward and accessible, but human poetry's complexity is part of its appeal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;: AI-generated poems might increase interest in poetry among non-experts, but true poetry involves elements beyond what AI can produce.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert Opinion&lt;/strong&gt;: Poet Joelle Taylor argues that true poetry involves empathy and revelation, which AI cannot fully capture.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;4. Overall Recommendation Degree: B&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pros&lt;/strong&gt;:
- The study provides valuable insights into how non-expert readers perceive AI-generated poetry.
- The methodology is clear and well-explained.
- The discussion includes both the strengths and limitations of AI-generated poetry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cons&lt;/strong&gt;:
- The sample of famous poets is limited to a specific demographic (white, male, middle-upper class), which may not represent the full spectrum of poetry.
- The study does not delve deeply into the technical aspects of how AI generates poetry.
- The conclusion that AI-generated poems might increase interest in poetry is speculative and lacks empirical support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;5. Who May Be Interested in This Content&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Researchers in AI and natural language processing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Poets and poetry enthusiasts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Educators and students studying literature and creative writing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Policymakers interested in AI regulation and transparency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;6. Thought-Provoking Questions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the key differences between human-written and AI-generated poetry that make them appealing to different types of readers?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How might the preference for AI-generated poetry among non-expert readers impact the future of poetry as an art form?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What elements of poetry, such as empathy and revelation, do you believe AI is currently unable to replicate, and why?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 21:36:56 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.theguardian.com/books/2024/nov/18/ai-poetry-rated-better-than-poems-written-by-humans-study-shows</guid></item><item><title>If you can’t trust the voice of David Attenborough, what can you trust? | Zoe Williams</title><description>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. Keywords&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;David Attenborough&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI Voice Cloning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Misuse&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2. Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The article discusses the ethical and legal implications of AI voice cloning, particularly focusing on the misuse of the voice of renowned naturalist David Attenborough. It highlights how AI technology has been used to create and disseminate false narratives, such as claims about Russia and the U.S. election, which Attenborough would never endorse. The piece also touches on similar cases involving other celebrities like Scarlett Johansson, where AI developers have faced legal challenges. The author emphasizes the broader concern that AI voice cloning could erode public trust in spoken information, making it difficult to discern what is real and what is fabricated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;3. Outline&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;: The article opens with the startling reality of AI voice cloning and its potential misuse, specifically mentioning David Attenborough.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Case Study: David Attenborough&lt;/strong&gt;: Various websites and YouTube channels are using AI to clone Attenborough's voice to spread misinformation about topics like Russia and the U.S. election.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Legal and Ethical Implications&lt;/strong&gt;: The article discusses the legal battles surrounding AI voice cloning, including the case of Scarlett Johansson and the response from OpenAI regarding the character "Sky."&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Broader Concerns&lt;/strong&gt;: The author raises concerns about the erosion of trust in spoken information due to the increasing sophistication of AI voice cloning technology.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;: The article concludes by emphasizing the need for regulation and public awareness to combat the misuse of AI voice cloning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;4. Overall Recommendation Degree: B&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pros:&lt;/strong&gt;
- The article effectively highlights a significant and timely issue related to AI and its potential misuse.
- It provides concrete examples and context, making the topic accessible and relevant to a broad audience.
- The writing is clear and engaging, maintaining the reader's interest throughout.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cons:&lt;/strong&gt;
- The article could benefit from more detailed exploration of the technical aspects of AI voice cloning.
- It lacks a comprehensive discussion of potential solutions or regulatory measures that could address the issues raised.
- The legal and ethical implications are touched upon but not deeply analyzed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;5. Who May Be Interested in This Content?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tech Enthusiasts and Professionals&lt;/strong&gt;: Those interested in AI and its applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Legal Experts&lt;/strong&gt;: Individuals concerned with intellectual property and digital rights.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Journalists and Media Consumers&lt;/strong&gt;: People who want to stay informed about the integrity of information in the digital age.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ethicists and Philosophers&lt;/strong&gt;: Those interested in the ethical implications of emerging technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;6. Thought-Provoking Questions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the potential long-term consequences of widespread AI voice cloning on public trust in media and information?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How should legal systems adapt to protect individuals' voices and prevent their misuse in AI-generated content?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What role can technology companies play in ensuring the ethical use of AI voice cloning, and what responsibilities do they have to their users and the public?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 21:36:33 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2024/nov/18/cant-trust-voice-david-attenborough-what-can-you-trust-ai</guid></item><item><title>AI Must Be Anti-Ableist and Accessible</title><description>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. Keywords&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accessibility&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ableism&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bias&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2. Summary&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The article discusses the critical issue of ableism in AI-based technologies and the potential negative impacts on disabled people. It highlights how AI systems can perpetuate and amplify biases against disabled individuals through unrepresentative data, missing or unlabeled data, measurement errors, and inaccessible interactions. The authors emphasize the importance of recognizing and addressing these biases to ensure that AI systems do not marginalize or harm disabled people. They propose several recommendations, including regulatory interventions, involving disabled people in the design and development of AI systems, and ensuring equitable data collection and management. The article concludes by stressing the need for a comprehensive approach to creating accessible and inclusive AI, drawing parallels with the disability rights movement and the development of accessibility tools in the computing industry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;3. Outline&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;: The increasing use of AI in everyday settings creates new opportunities and challenges for understanding how disabled people might use these technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Defining Disability&lt;/strong&gt;: Disability is defined in terms of systemic problems with infrastructure and its ability to meet the needs of people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recognizing and Addressing Disability Bias in AI-Based Systems&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unrepresentative Data&lt;/strong&gt;: AI models may be biased due to underrepresentation of marginalized groups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Missing or Unlabeled Data&lt;/strong&gt;: AI models trained on existing data may reproduce biases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Measurement Error&lt;/strong&gt;: Errors in measurement can exacerbate bias.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inaccessible Interactions&lt;/strong&gt;: Even well-designed systems may have inaccessible interfaces.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disability-Specific Harms of AI-Based Technologies&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Defining "Human"&lt;/strong&gt;: AI systems may render disabled people invisible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Defining "Counts" as Disabled&lt;/strong&gt;: AI may rely on historical medical definitions of disability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exacerbating and Causing Disability&lt;/strong&gt;: AI systems may physically harm or limit access to resources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy and Security&lt;/strong&gt;: AI can detect disability status and track progression without consent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reinforcing Ableist Policies&lt;/strong&gt;: AI systems may reinforce ableist attitudes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recommendations&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Regulatory Intervention&lt;/strong&gt;: Algorithms should be subject to basic accessibility standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Involving Disabled People&lt;/strong&gt;: Disabled people should contribute to the design and development of AI systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Equitable Data Collection&lt;/strong&gt;: Data collection should be equitable and transparent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Representation&lt;/strong&gt;: Community involvement can improve data collection and system design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assessment Methods&lt;/strong&gt;: Develop methods to uncover and address bias.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;: Creating accessible AI is a question of values and requires a comprehensive approach, similar to the disability rights movement and the development of accessibility tools in computing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;4. Overall Recommendation Degree: B&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pros&lt;/strong&gt;:
- The article comprehensively addresses the issue of ableism in AI and provides a detailed analysis of the various forms of bias.
- It offers practical recommendations for addressing these issues, emphasizing the importance of involving disabled people in the design and development process.
- The article draws valuable parallels with the disability rights movement and the development of accessibility tools in computing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cons&lt;/strong&gt;:
- The article could benefit from more concrete examples of successful interventions and case studies.
- Some sections, particularly those discussing technical aspects, could be more accessible to a general audience.
- The article does not delve deeply into the potential economic and social benefits of creating accessible AI, which could strengthen its argument.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;5. Who May Be Interested in This Content&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI Developers and Researchers&lt;/strong&gt;: Those involved in the development and deployment of AI systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Policy Makers and Regulators&lt;/strong&gt;: Individuals responsible for creating and enforcing regulations related to AI and accessibility.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disability Advocates and Activists&lt;/strong&gt;: People working to improve the lives of disabled individuals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ethicists and Social Scientists&lt;/strong&gt;: Scholars interested in the ethical implications of AI and technology.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;6. Thought-Provoking Questions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How can we ensure that AI systems are designed and tested with the input of disabled people to avoid ableist biases?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the potential consequences of failing to address ableism in AI, both for disabled individuals and society at large?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How can we balance the need for privacy and security with the necessity of collecting and using data to improve AI systems for disabled people?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 21:36:13 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://cacm.acm.org/opinion/ai-must-be-anti-ableist-and-accessible/</guid></item></channel></rss>